Guide to the North Carolina Council of Churches records, 1935-2019 RL.00934
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2001-0100)
  - Daycare Center for Elderly--Project Site (Box 60)
  - Members Attending Conference Listed (Box 60)
  - Downtown Church Center, Winston-Salem (Box 60)
  - Drake University (Box 60)
  - Conference Resource People (Box 60)
  - Duke University Divinity School (Box 60)
  - Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development--Duke University Medical Center (Box 60)
  - Ecumenical Organizations in NC Leaders (Box 60)
  - Clergy Conference Registration (Box 60)
  - Clergy Conference on Aging--Greensboro, NC (Box 60)
  - Episcopal Community Services (Box 60)
  - Episcopal Society for the Ministry for the Aging, Incorporated (Box 60)
  - Mr. Charles Fraizer--Executive Secretary (Box 60)
  - Reverend W.W. Finlator (Box 60)
  - Edna McConell Clark Foundation (Box 60)
  - Cathedral Foundation Jacksonville, Florida (Box 60)
  - First Christian Church (Box 60)
  - Friends General Conference (Box 60)
  - Grants Received (Box 60)
  - Governor's Council on Aging Raleigh Office (Box 60)
  - Speaker's Bureau of Governor Council on Aging (Box 60)
  - Food-stamp Outreach (Box 60)
  - UNC--Greensboro--Project Application (Box 60)
  - Guilford County Council on Aging (Mr. John Conrad, High Point Coordinator) (Box 60)
  - NICA National Interfaith Coalition on Aging (Box 60)
  - Interfaith Coalitions
    - Interfaith Coalition on Family Financial Planning (Box 60)
    - Interfaith Commission on Aging of Missouri Council of Churches (Box 60)
    - National Interfaith Coalition, Washington, DC (Box 60)
    - Nash--Edgecombe Interfaith Coalition on Aging (Box 60)
    - Inter-church Council for Social Services, Nursing Home Visitation Program (Box 60)
    - INCC Interreligious New Communities Coalition (Box 60)
    - Raleigh Interfaith Coalition on Aging (Box 60)
  - Illinois Interfaith Coalition on Aging (Box 61)
  - Pinellas County Interfaith Coalition on Aging (Box 61)
  - Jewish Synagogues Miscellaneous (Box 61)
  - NC Jewish Home--Mr. Elbert E. Levy, Executive Director (Box 61)
  - Kendall Foundation (Box 61)
  - Elizabeth D. Koontz--Department of Human Resources (Box 61)
  - Lake Junaluska Assambly (Box 61)
  - Lutheran Church in America (Box 61)
  - Rev. Ed. McNulty, Bethel Presbyterian Church, Bethel Park, PA (Box 61)
  - Model Project Advisory Committee, 1975 May 28 (Box 61)
  - Audio-Visual (Box 61)
  - Baptist Churches--General (Box 61)
  - Rev. Phillip S. Brown, Director Penick Episcopal Home for the Aging, Southern Pines, NC (Box 61)
  - Booklets, Pamphlets Requested from Others (Box 61)
  - Baptist State Convention (Box 61)
  - Miss Isabelle Buckley (Box 61)
  - Curriculum (Box 61)
  - Clergy Training Program (Box 61)
  - Charlotte Area Clergy Association (Box 61)
  - Church Architecture--NCSU School of Design (Box 61)
  - Community Colleges and Continuing Education Project (Box 61)
  - Clinical Pastoral Education (CPE) Trained Ministers--One Year Plus (Partial List) (Box 61)
  - Councils of Churches
    - Churches Listed for Questionnaire for Newsletter, January 1975 (Box 61)
    - Interdenominational Leaders in North Carolina Member Bodies (Box 61)
    - Commission on Christian Nurture (Box 61)
    - Executive Board Annual Meeting (Box 61)
    - Statement of Income and Expense 1975 January-1975 March (Box 61)
    - Dr. Samuel F. Wiley, Executive Director (Box 61)
    - Commission on Christian Unity (Box 61)
    - General (Box 61)
    - Florida Council of Churches (Box 61)
    - Virginia Council of Churches (Box 61)
    - County Councils of Governments (Box 61)
    - Conferences or Meetings--Proposed (Box 61)
  - Conferences, Conventions and Meetings
    - Region IV Symposium on Aging--Atlanta, GA 1974 November 20-1974 November 22 (Box 61)
    - Conference--Charlotte December 4 1974 (Box 61)
    - Clergy Conference on Aging--Southern Pines 1974 December 12 (Box 61)
    - Meeting 1974 December 15 (Box 61)
    - Area IV Conference 1974 December 20-1974 December 22 (Box 61)
    - The National Council on the Aging 1974 September 29-1974 October 2 (Box 61)
    - Legislative Seminar 1975 January 8 (Box 61)
    - Kansas City Meeting--January, NICA for Directors (Box 61)
    - Umstead Lecture Notes 1975 February 5-1975 February 6 (Box 61)
    - Family Life Conference--Tarboro 1975 March 5Rev. Caswell R. Shaw, Chairman (Box 61)
    - Non-profit Nursing Home Association Meeting 1975 February (Box 61)
    - Training Session in Fayetteville 1975 March 22 (Box 61)
    - Urban Encounter--Fayetteville 1975 March 1 (Box 61)
    - 3rd Annual Caucus on Black Aged--Washington, DC 1975 April 13-1975 April 15 (Box 61)
    - Region IV Symposia on Aging--Greenville, SC 1975 April 16-1975 April 18 (Box 61)
    - Planning Conference 1975 May 8 (Box 61)
    - Advisory Committee Meeting--College Inn, Raleigh 1975 February 17 (Box 61)
  - Mr. E.B. Hobgood, Treasurer, two folders (Box 61)
  - 1945 Finance (Box 61)
  - NC CROP, 1952-1955 (Box 61)
  - Ledger, 1954-1955 (Box 61)
  - Petty Cash, 1954-1955 (Box 61)
  - Expenses and Receipts (Box 61)
  - Finances--CWS and CROP, 1954, three folders (Box 61)
  - Paid Bills (Alphabetical order from R to Z), 1956-1959, seven folders (Box 61)
  - Reconciliations, 1958-1959 (Box 61)
  - Bank Reconciliation Statements Fiscal Year, 1957 (Box 61)
  - Camp Registrations (Box 61)
  - Family Life Conference, 1959 April 20-1959 April 21 (Box 61)
  - Finance Letters, 1958 (Box 61)
  - Finance Foundations (Box 61)
  - Finance (Box 62)
    - Budget for 1952 (Box 62)
    - Accounts paid--Addressograph-Multigraph Corp. (Box 62)
    - Overseas Relief Displaced Persons (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Mr. Arnold (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Association of Council Secretaries (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Carolina Supply Company (Box 62)
    - Solicitations--Overseas Relief (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Carolina Printing Company (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Contributions (Box 62)
    - Councils Publishers Club (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Dictaphone Corporation (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Duke University, three folders (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Durham Engraving Company (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Durham Office Supply (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Durham Printery (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Durham Telephone Company (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Expenses of Committee Chairmen and Members (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Federal Council of Churches (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Gray and Creech, Inc. (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--National Council of Churches of Christ (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--National School Supply Company Inc. (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Piedmont Press (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Presbyterian Committee of Publication (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid-- 1948 Relief Drive Expense Accounts (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Rural (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Service Printing Company (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Subscriptions (Box 62)
    - Query Expense Account (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--US Post Office (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--United Council of Churchwomen (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Women (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Youth (Box 62)
    - Receipts not Mailed Out (Box 62)
    - The Friendship Press Exhibit Membership (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--International Council of Religious Education (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Methodist Publishing House (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Miscellaneous (Box 62)
    - Accounts Paid--Missionary Education Movement (Box 62)
    - Receipt Book 1952-1957 (Box 62)
    - NC CROP Receipts 1952-1954, two folders (Box 62)
    - Fidelity Bank Record of Receipts for CSA Project 1963 (Box 62)
    - Record of Receipts for Social Action Director 1964 (Box 62)
  - Pastors' Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 63)
  - Pastors' Conference (Annual Meeting), 1955-1955 (Box 63)
  - Alcohol Institute (Box 63)
  - General Correspondence, Councils Publishers Club (Box 63)
  - General: Dairy Council (Box 63)
  - World Council of Churches (Evanston, 1954) (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee-- 1957 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1955 October 6 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1954 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee--General (Box 63)
  - Foreign Students--Present (Box 63)
  - Foreign Students, 1959 (Box 63)
  - Foreign Students, 1956 (Box 63)
  - Foreign Students Attending NC Colleges and Universities Past (Box 63)
  - Town and Country Commision (Box 63)
  - Committee on Rural Church, two folders (Box 63)
  - Farm and Home Week, 1955 (Box 63)
  - Pastoral Ministry Commission, 1953-1959, two folders (Box 63)
  - Pastoral Ministry Commission, 1955-1957 (Box 63)
  - Rural Church, three folders (Box 63)
  - Constitutional Committee 1952 (Box 63)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1952-1953 (Box 63)
  - Advisory Committee, 1952-1956 (Box 63)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box 63)
  - Heifer Project, 1952-1956 (Box 63)
  - Legal Aide Clinic (Box 63)
  - Evangelism, 1951-1959, two folders (Box 63)
  - Church Survey, 1957 (Box 63)
  - Commission on Home Missions and Evangelism (Box 63)
  - Church Survey (Box 63)
  - Inter-Church Projects (Box 63)
  - Radio--TV (Box 64)
    - Workshops--General, two folders (Box 64)
    - Committee, two folders (Box 64)
    - Workshop Wilmington (Box 64)
    - General Information (Box 64)
    - Workshop Durham (Box 64)
    - Workshop Asheville (Box 64)
    - Workshop Greenville (Box 64)
    - General Workshop (Box 64)
    - Workshop Winston-Salem (Box 64)
  - Church Woman United
    - Copies of Annual Meeting Bulletin 1956-1970, Foward and History of C.W.U. in NC (Box 64)
    - Newsletter, three folders (Box 64)
    - 1944-1952, two folders (Box 64)
    - Church Women United, five folders (Box 64)
    - Family Life Committee, two folders (Box 64)
    - RSVBO: Concord and Chapel Hill (Sample Communities) (Box 64)
    - Reports of Weekday Committee of NC Council 1946-1950 (Box 64)
  - Official Membership of the North Carolina Council Of Churches (Box 65)
  - Migrant Ministry
    - Welfare, State Department of, Ellen G. Winston, Commissioner (Box 65)
    - Committee Meeting (Box 65)
    - Migrant Ministry, five folders, some material removed to oversize box (Box 65)
    - Migrant Reports 1964, four folders (Box 65)
    - 1966 October-1967 October, four folders (Box 65)
    - Loose Material, seven folders (Box 65)
    - Migrant Health (Box 65)
    - Eastern Regional Migrant Ministry Conference (Box 65)
  - Migrant Ministry (Box 66)
    - Economic Opportunity, five folders (Box 66)
    - Ministry to Migrants, five folders (Box 66)
    - Loose Material 1969-1979, twelve folders (Box 66)
  - Loose materials, eighteen folders (Box 67)
  - Annual Meeting, Report of Activities, 1946-1947, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Annual Meeting, Report of Activities, 1956-1966 (Box 67)
  - Newsletter, 1959-1964 (Box 67)
  - UCW Pamphlets (Box 67)
  - Scraps from Caswell Bible (Box 67)
  - Church Council Bulletin, 1965 December-1969 December, twenty-seven folders (Box 68)
  - Church Council Bulletin, 1964 June-1965 October, eight folders (Box 69)
  - Bible Department, 1944-1945 (Box 69)
  - Annual Meeting, 1964-1968, eight folders (Box 69)
  - Reidsville (Box 69)
  - National and World Affairs--Continued, two folders (Box 69)
  - Methodist Church WNC Conference 1964-1967, two folders (Box 69)
  - Citizens' Council (Box 69)
  - Operation/World's Fair (Box 69)
  - Regional Children's Conference, two folders (Box 69)
  - Seminar on Church and Community, 1968 (Box 69)
  - Communism, 1958-1967 (Box 69)
  - Communism, 1967-1968 (Box 69)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1964-1965 (Box 69)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1966-1967 (Box 69)
  - Seminar on Church and Community, 1968 Registrations (Box 69)
  - Statewide Churchmen's Conference on Civil Rights, 1965-1966 (Box 69)
  - Seminar on Church and Community--Mimeographed Materials (Box 69)
  - Technology and Human Values, three folders (Box 70)
  - United Church Women, 1964-1967, six folders (Box 70)
  - Informers--Steering Committee (Box 70)
  - Materials from the National Office of UCYM (Box 70)
  - Informer--General Information (Box 70)
  - Sam Mann (Box 70)
  - NAEYA, 1961 (Box 70)
  - Mail (Box 70)
  - Names for the Informers (Box 70)
  - Southern Baptist (Box 70)
  - United Presbyterian USA (Catawba Synod) (Box 70)
  - North Carolina Ecumenical Youth Assembly (Box 70)
  - EXEC Complex (Box 70)
  - Association of Council Secretaries (Box 70)
  - Audio-Visual (Box 70)
  - Background Work of NC Council (Box 70)
  - Episcopal (East Carolina Diocese) (Box 70)
  - Episcopal (North Carolina Diocese) (Box 70)
  - Episcopal (Western North Carolina Diocese) (Box 70)
  - Lutheran (Box 70)
  - Methodist (WNC Conference) (Box 70)
  - Evangelical and Reformed (Box 70)
  - Friends (Box 70)
  - Methodist (NC Conference) (Box 70)
  - General Baptist (Box 70)
  - Moravian (Box 70)
  - Presbyterian US (Asheville Presbyterian) (Box 70)
  - Presbyterian US (Synod of North Carolina) (Box 70)
  - Disciples of Christ (Box 70)
  - Smithfield (Box 70)
  - Statesville (Box 70)
  - Swannanoa (Box 70)
  - Tarboro (Box 70)
  - Tomasville (Box 70)
  - Warrenton (Box 70)
  - Washington (Box 70)
  - Winston-Salem (Box 70)
  - AMEZ (Box 70)
  - ARP (Box 70)
  - CME (Box 70)
  - Church of the Brethren (Box 70)
  - Church of God (Box 70)
  - Congregational Christian (Convention of the South) (Box 70)
  - Cogregational Christian (Southern Convention) (Box 70)
  - Oxford (Box 70)
  - Plymouth (Box 70)
  - Red Springs (Box 70)
  - Hamlet (Box 71)
  - Siler City (Box 71)
  - Sanford (Box 71)
  - Halifax / Welden (Box 71)
  - Greenville (Box 71)
  - Greensboro (Box 71)
  - Henderson (Box 71)
  - Hyde County (Box 71)
  - Jacksonville (Box 71)
  - Kannapolis (Box 71)
  - King's Mountain (Box 71)
  - Fayetteville (Box 71)
  - Lillington (Box 71)
  - Lumberton (Box 71)
  - Mebane (Box 71)
  - Monroe (Box 71)
  - Mooresville (Box 71)
  - Mount Airy (Box 71)
  - North Wilkesboro (Box 71)
  - New Bern (Box 71)
  - Forest City (Box 71)
  - Gates County (Box 71)
  - Gastonia (Box 71)
  - Kinston (Box 71)
  - Goldsboro (Box 71)
  - Raleigh (Box 71)
  - Farmville (Box 71)
  - Roanoke Rapids (Box 71)
  - Reidsville (Box 71)
  - Wilmington (Box 71)
  - Wilson (Box 71)
  - Potential Councils (Box 71)
  - Andrews (Box 71)
  - Ashville (Box 71)
  - Beaufort (Box 71)
  - Burgaw, two folders (Box 71)
  - Charlotte (Box 71)
  - Concord (Box 71)
  - Durham (Box 71)
  - Fairmount (Box 71)
  - Dunn (Box 71)
  - Committee on Youth Work NC (Box 71)
  - Committee on Youth work (Box 71)
  - Citizenship Commission (Box 71)
  - Faith Commission (Box 71)
  - National Committee on Youth Work (Box 71)
  - CWS (Box 71)
  - Current Constitution (Box 71)
  - Correspondence
    - UCYM--Pending (Box 71)
    - Correspondence (Box 71)
    - Executive Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 71)
    - NCUCYM--Executive Committee 1958-1959 (Box 71)
    - NCUCYM--Executive Officers and Council 1961-1962 (Box 71)
    - Executive Board: NCCC (Box 71)
  - Local Council Officers (Box 71)
  - State Officers Lists (Box 71)
  - NCUCYM State Council (Box 71)
  - Local Council Organization Education (Box 71)
  - Local Council Contacts (Box 71)
  - Council--How to Plan (Box 71)
  - Local Councils, Information on Each (Box 71)
  - Burlington (Box 71)
  - Chapel Hill (Box 71)
  - Fellowship Commission (Box 71)
  - Outreach Commission (Box 71)
  - Witness Commission (Box 71)
  - Yearbook of American Churches, Letter (Box 71)
  - Material on the Five Commissions (Box 71)
  - Fall Assembly--Raleigh, 1961 (Box 71)
  - NCUCYM--Spring Assembly Registrations, 1962 (Box 71)
  - Old Letters and Minutes, 1968-1964, two folders (Box 71)
  - Public Affairs Committee 1959, two folders (Box 71)
  - Youth Student Ecumenical Conference--Chapel Hill (Box 71)
  - Records, 1949-1950 From Youth Book (Box 71)
  - UCYM Regional, 1950 (Box 71)
  - Eastern CYCNC Rally (Box 71)
  - White House Conference (Box 71)
  - American Bible Society, two folders (Box 71)
  - Annual Meetings, 1950-1959, nineteen folders (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 72)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1951 January 29 (Box 72)
  - Committee on Comity (Box 72)
  - Committee on Promotion and public relations (Box 72)
  - Bible Department NCEA (Box 72)
  - Bible Department NCTA (Box 72)
  - Radio and TV General information, 1940-1953 (Box 72)
  - Radio and Teaching (Box 72)
  - Kurtz--General Correspondence, two folders (Box 72)
  - Vatican Appointment, 1951-1952 (Box 72)
  - Washington Pilgrimage (Box 72)
  - Save the Children (Box 72)
  - Ministry with the Aging (Box 73)
    - Governor's Conference on the Quality of Life for Our Senior Citizens (Box 73)
    - Financial (Box 73)
    - Project SSI-Alert (Box 73)
    - General Correspondence (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous, three folders (Box 73)
    - Accepted--Blacks and Minority (Box 73)
    - Declined--Blacks Not Heard From (Box 73)
    - Accepted--White (Box 73)
    - Declined--Whites Not Heard From (Box 73)
    - Spiritual Well-Being Conference (Box 73)
    - Richard F. McCleery (Box 73)
    - North Carolina Governor's Coordinating Council on Aging (Box 73)
    - Spiritual Well-Being (Box 73)
    - Conference on the Spiritual Well-Being of the Aging (Box 73)
    - Older Adults (Box 73)
    - Aging, two folders (Box 73)
  - The Antkeeper, 1967 (Box 73)
  - Appalachian Regional School for Church Leaders, 1968 (Box 73)
  - Boycott, 1968-1969 (Box 73)
  - Alcohol and Narcotics, 1964-1967 (Box 73)
  - Alcohol and Narcotics Committee 1964-1967, continued from previous box (Box 74)
  - Christian Social Action, 1967-1967, eleven folders (Box 74)
  - Committee of Concern (Box 74)
  - Dr. Samuel E. Duncan (Box 74)
  - Educational Testing Service (Box 74)
  - A Fellowship on Concern (Box 74)
  - Henderson, Robert T. (Box 74)
  - Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1964-1968, three folders (Box 74)
  - Human Relations Committee, four folders (Box 74)
  - Church of the Brethren, three folders (Box 74)
  - Episcopal Diocese of North Carolina 1967-1968, four folders (Box 75)
  - Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 75)
  - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ) (Box 75)
  - Baptist Church, three folders (Box 75)
  - AME Church (Box 75)
  - AME Zion Church (Box 75)
  - Associate Reformed Presbyterian (Box 75)
  - General Baptist State Convention (Box 75)
  - Souther Baptist Churches (Box 75)
  - Samuel S. Wiley--Durham NC (Box 75)
  - Episcopal Diocese of Western North Carolina (Box 75)
  - Episcopal Diocese of Eastern North Carolina (Box 75)
  - Lutheran Church in America, two folders (Box 75)
  - Friends NC Yearly Meeting, two folders (Box 75)
  - Salvation Army (Box 75)
  - Presbytery of Asheville US (Box 75)
  - Presbytery of Holston US (Box 75)
  - Methodist Church Central Jurisdiction (Box 76)
  - Methodist, North Carolina Conference (Box 76)
  - Finance--North Carolina Conference, The Methodist Church (Box 76)
  - WNC Conference, The United Methodist Church (Contributions) (Box 76)
  - Moravian Church (Box 76)
  - Presbytery of Holston UP USA (Box 76)
  - The Methodist Church--Western NC Conference, four folders (Box 76)
  - Methodist Church NC Conference, two folders (Box 76)
  - Congregational Christian Church (Box 76)
  - United Presbyterian Church USA (Box 76)
  - United Church of Christ, three folders (Box 76)
  - Peace Booth--NC State Fair (Box 76)
  - Poverty Program (Box 76)
  - Prayer Ammendment (Box 76)
  - Publications (Box 76)
  - Panel Representing Cooperative Work (Box 76)
  - Sam Reed (Box 76)
  - Reformed Church in America (Box 76)
  - Religion and the Arts, two folders (Box 76)
  - Religion in American Life (Box 76)
  - Renewal of the Council (Box 76)
  - Research and Strategy (Box 76)
  - Planned Parenthood Program (Box 76)
  - Planned Parenthood (Box 76)
  - Political Candidates (Box 76)
  - Political Action in Christ (PAX) (Box 76)
  - Shared Staff (Box 76)
  - Shared Time Religious Instruction Task Force (Box 76)
  - Miss Becky Short, Miss Mary Lou Yancey (Box 76)
  - Southern Committee on the Education of Children (Box 76)
  - Social Education and Political Issues Task Force (CORA) (Box 76)
  - Resort Area Ministry (Box 76)
  - Southern Regional Council (Box 76)
  - Study Opportunities (Box 76)
  - Suburban Partners (Box 76)
  - Samarcand Manor Chapel Fund (Box 76)
  - Thanksgiving 1977 (Box 76)
  - Traffic Safety Sabbath, 1974 (Box 77)
  - Twin Streams (Box 77)
  - Dr. Raymond U (Box 77)
  - United Durham, Inc. (Box 77)
  - Urban Policy Study (Box 77)
  - Vocations (Box 77)
  - Welfare and Health Policies for the Future, 1971 (Box 77)
  - George. R. Whittecar (Box 77)
  - WRAL - Channel 5 (Box 77)
  - School Desegregation, 1972 (Box 77)
  - Women-in-Action For the Prevention of Violence and its Causes, Incorporated (Box 77)
  - World Affairs Institute - Southeastern (Box 77)
  - World Council of Churches, 1962-1970 (Box 77)
  - World Wide Communion (Box 77)
  - Robert W. Scott (Box 77)
  - Migrant Ministry, 1975, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Yokefellow Movement, 1978, 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Migrant Project, 3 folders (Box 77)
  - Target Area Council - Bylaws (Box 77)
  - Annual Report, 1970 (Box 77)
  - Seminar on Church and Community, 1969-1971, 6 folders (Box 77)
  - Communications Awards, 1974-1978, 10 folders (Box 77)
  - Communications Awards, 1963-1972, 8 folders (Box 78)
  - House of Delegates, 1978, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Annual Meetings, 1973-1977, 17 folders (Box 78)
  - Malcom X University (Box 78)
  - Mennonites (Box 78)
  - Mental Health (Box 78)
  - Mars Hill (Box 78)
  - Resources, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Mental Retardation, 5 folders (Box 78)
  - Ministry in Institutions, 1968, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Ministerial Associations and Councils of Churches (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Letters, 1964 (Box 78)
  - Mental Retardation Seminar, 1971, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - National and World Affairs, 1971 (Box 79)
  - Subject/Office Files, M-O, 1964-1974, 11 folders (Box 79)
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes Operation Interface
  - World Affairs Committee, 1964, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Outer Banks (Box 79)
  - Oxford (Box 79)
  - Training Conference, 1957 (Box 79)
  - Office of Publication and Distribution (Box 79)
  - Training Conference, 1958 (Box 79)
  - Other State Councils (Box 79)
  - NC Council of Churches (Box 79)
  - Bulletin, 1956 (Box 79)
  - United Christian Youth Mission, 1952 (Box 79)
  - World Youth Projects, 1952-1956, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Training Conference, 1958, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Programs (Box 79)
  - National UCYM Information (Box 79)
  - Projects - Misc. (Box 79)
  - Traffic Safety (Box 79)
  - National Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 79)
  - Commission Material (Box 79)
  - Constitution of National UCYM (Box 79)
  - National Council of Churches (World) (Box 79)
  - Look Up and Live (Box 79)
  - Field Representatives, 1956-1957 (Box 79)
  - National Correspondence, 1954 (Box 79)
  - Leaders of States in UCYM, 1953 (Box 79)
  - National UCYM - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 80)
  - National Correspondence, 1957-1959, 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Christian Youth Council Bulletins "The Informer", 1953-1957, 5 folders (Box 80)
  - Advisory Committee, 1975, 4 folders (Box 80)
  - Survey on Clergy Attitudes Towards Aging (Box 80)
  - Social Security (Box 80)
  - School of Social Work (Box 80)
  - Pensions (Box 80)
  - Advisory Committee, 1975, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - U.S. House of Representatives (Box 80)
  - Purchases, 1975 (Box 80)
  - NRTA/AARP (Box 80)
  - Newsletter, 1975, 13 folders (Box 80)
  - Finance, 1975 (Box 80)
  - Yale Univ. Divinity School, Father Henri Nouwen (Box 80)
  - Yokefellow Prison Ministry of N.C. (Box 80)
  - Population Older Parish Survey (Box 80)